wagerline.com 2006-04-13

# Wagerline.com - FREE Real-time Scores, Odds, & Contests for All Major Sports

WagerLine.com is owned and operated by SportsDirect Inc.   This statement demonstrates our commitment to privacy.  It discloses the information collected by SportsDirect Inc. in the operation of WagerLine.com.

SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information of non-employee Persons who interact with SportsDirect Inc. that is collected, used or disclosed SportsDirect Inc. 

Non-employee Persons in this context includes Individuals who are viewers, readers, subscribers, advertisers, contest participants, forum members, customers, Internet users who are exposed to the media and e-commerce content of SportsDirect Inc. 

The SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy applies to the management of Personal Information in any form whether oral, electronic or written. SportsDirect Inc. reserves the right to amend this SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy from time to time. 

The application of the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy is subject to the requirements or provisions of any applicable legislation, regulations or agreements, or the order of any court or other lawful authority. 

**Exclusions from privacy protection:** The SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy does not impose any limits on the collection, use or disclosure of the following information by SportsDirect Inc.: 

a) Information which is available publicly, such as a Person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; 

b) Information collected, used or disclosed in the course of journalistic, literary or artistic activities; or 

c) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about SportsDirect Inc. customers, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website. 

### Purposes for Collection of Personal Information: 

SportsDirect Inc. has collected and collects Personal Information for the following purposes: 

a) To establish and maintain responsible commercial relations with Individuals and to provide ongoing service; 

b) To understand Individual needs; 

c) To enhance, develop, market or provide products and services; and 

d) To meet legal or regulatory requirements, including to protect or defend a legal interest, and in connection with an actual or possible SportsDirect Inc. corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or an actual or possible sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of SportsDirect Inc., provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used by the entity acquiring the information either for evaluation of the possible transaction, or, on completion of any such transaction, for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

As examples of the above: 

i) SportsDirect Inc. may from time to time use a Person's Personal Information to contact the Person about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to SportsDirect Inc. products and services; 

ii) If a Person indicated that they were interested in receiving offers or information from SportsDirect Inc. or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, SportsDirect Inc. may send the Person materials about products and services that SportsDirect Inc. feels may be of interest to the Person; and 

iii) If a Person enters a contest or other promotion offered on a SportsDirect Inc. website, SportsDirect Inc. may, under the rules of the promotion, use the Person's name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion. 

### Obtaining Consent: 

SportsDirect Inc. will make a reasonable effort to make sure Persons understand how their Personal Information will be used by SportsDirect Inc.. SportsDirect Inc. will obtain consent from Persons before or when it collects or uses the Personal Information. SportsDirect Inc. will not attempt to deceive Persons into giving consent. 

A Person's consent can be express, implied, or given through an authorized representative. A Person can withdraw consent at any time, with certain exceptions noted herein. SportsDirect Inc., however, may collect, use or disclose Personal Information without the Person's knowledge or consent in exceptional circumstances where such collection, use or disclosure is permitted or as required by law. 

**Note:** If any Person has any questions or concerns about SportsDirect Inc.'s privacy practices, the Person can either: 

i) Write to Customer Service - Privacy, SportsDirect Inc., 77 Chain Lake Drive, Halifax, NS, B3S 1E1; or 

ii) Provide information to SportsDirect Inc. through the form provided on our  feedback page . 

### Refusing or withdrawing Consent: 

Subject to legal and contractual requirements, a Person can refuse to consent to SportsDirect Inc.'s collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information about the Person, or a Person may withdraw the Person's consent to SportsDirect Inc.'s further collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information at any time in the future by giving SportsDirect Inc. reasonable notice, unless: 

i) The consent relates to certain information required for credit approval which a Person applies for or accepts,   

ii) The consent is otherwise required by law or iii) the use or disclosure is permitted by law or is related to the legal or regulatory requirements described herein. If a Person refuses or withdraws the Person's consent, SportsDirect Inc. may not be able to provide the Person or continue to provide the Person with some products, services or information which may be of value to the Person. 

### Internet Aspects: 

Personal Information may be collected when a user conducts activities on or related to all websites of SportsDirect Inc. (see "SportsDirect Inc. Companies Sites") or related to services made available on the SportsDirect Inc. Companies Sites. Although information collected, used or disclosed on the Internet as described below often does not constitute Personal Information (and to the extent that such is the case, then the obligations under the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy do not extend to such information), SportsDirect Inc. provides the details below about Internet aspects of SportsDirect Inc. services for the purposes of disclosure. 

### Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) 

When the user's web browser requests a web page from another computer on the Internet, it automatically gives that computer the address where it should send the information. This address is called the computer's "IP address." For most users accessing the Internet from a dial-up Internet service provider (ISP), the IP address will be different every time the user logs on.   
SportsDirect Inc. may use the user's IP Address to: 

a) Facilitate the diagnosis and remedy of a technical problem reported by the user's or SportsDirect Inc's technical team. 

b) Display (or allow the display by Third Party advertising providers of) more appropriate and relevant content and advertising, such as content and advertising based on the user's geographic area. 

c) Estimate user traffic from specific countries or organizations. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers. 

### Cookies 

A cookie is a small text file, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to the user's web browser from a web site's computers and is stored on the user's computer's hard drive. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to a user's computer.   
SportsDirect Inc. may use cookies to: 

a) Improve the operation and performance of the SportsDirect Inc. services and to make SportsDirect Inc. services easier and more convenient to use. For example, cookies help SportsDirect Inc. provide more personalized services by recalling user preferences on subsequent visits (e.g. language preference). Cookies also allow SportsDirect Inc. to save passwords and preferences for a user so that the user will not have to re-enter them on the next visit to a SportsDirect Inc. website; 

b) Measure aggregate user traffic and demographic statistics related to SportsDirect Inc. websites and advertisements (e.g. number of users, average time spent, average age and similar statistics). This information helps SportsDirect Inc. to better understand when to update, change or offer new services and provides SportsDirect Inc. with details as to the performance of Third Party advertisements and content. This information may be reported, in aggregate form only, to SportsDirect Inc's current and prospective sponsors, advertisers and business partners. No Personal Information will be disclosed in such reports; 

c) Display advertisements. SportsDirect Inc. and Third Party advertising providers may use cookies when serving advertisements on SportsDirect Inc. websites. In some cases, advertisements from Third Party advertisers are delivered to users (in conjunction with SportsDirect Inc. services) by such Third Party advertisers, or by separately contracted advertising providers on their behalf, and not by SportsDirect Inc.; as such, the Third-party advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy, and users should consult the privacy policies of such Third Party advertisers. 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If a user prefers, the user can reset his/her browser either to notify the user when the user has received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. The user should understand that while SportsDirect Inc. do not require a user to use cookies, certain SportsDirect Inc. services will not function properly if a user sets his/her browser to not accept cookies. 

### Links To Other Sites And Advertisements 

A SportsDirect Inc. website may contain links to other websites and services. While SportsDirect Inc. try to link only to sites and services that share SportsDirect Inc's high standards and respect for privacy, a user should understand that SportsDirect Inc. is not responsible for the content of, or the privacy practices employed by, other companies or websites. This SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy applies only to the SportsDirect Inc. services related to this SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy. 

The majority of the advertisements which are displayed in connection with SportsDirect Inc. services are served through one or more reputable Third Party advertisement-serving companies which deliver the advertisements to users in conjunction with SportsDirect Inc. services. 

### Additional Information 

SportsDirect Inc. Companies automatically collect certain information about the user's computer hardware and software. This information may include: browser type, operating system type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by SportsDirect Inc. to operate the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SportsDirect Inc. Companies Sites. 

Certain SportsDirect Inc. services may be co-branded and offered in conjunction with another company. If a user registers for or uses such services, both SportsDirect Inc. and the other company may receive information collected in conjunction with the co-branded services. 

### SportsDirect Inc. Companies Sites 

Covers.com   
Coversexperts.com   
Sportsdirectinc.com   
Pokerfan.com  
Patmillersports.com   
Bgsports.com  
Williamfoote.com  
Davemalinsky.com  
Stevemerril.com  
Leonardsports.com  
Tonygeorgesports.com  
Torreysports.com  
Mattfargo.com  
Bigalsports.com  
Larrynesssports.com  
Wagerline.com  
Coversodds.com

**The SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy in Detail**

### Definitions 

**Collection** \- the act of gathering, acquiring, recording or obtaining Personal Information from any source, including third parties, by any means. 

**Consent** \- voluntary agreement with the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information for defined purposes. Consent can be either express or implied and can be provided directly by the Person or by an authorized representative. Express consent can be given orally, electronically or in writing but is always unequivocal and does not require any inference on the part of SportsDirect Inc.. Implied consent is consent that can reasonably be inferred from a Person's action or inaction. 

**Disclosure** \- making Personal Information available to a Third Party. 

**Individual** \- an individual other than an Employee who   
(a) Corresponds with SportsDirect Inc., including complaints and including applications for employment;   
(b) Enters a contest or forum sponsored by SportsDirect Inc.; or   
(c) Uses, or applies to use, the products or services of SportsDirect Inc.. 

**Person** \- an Individual. 

**Personal Information** \- information about an identifiable Person, but not:   
a) Information that is publicly available, such as a Person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance;   
b) Business-contact information, such as the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization;   
c) Information collected, used or disclosed in the course of journalistic, literary or artistic activities; or   
d) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about SportsDirect Inc. customers, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website. 

**Third Party** \- a person other than the Person or his agent, or an organization other than a SportsDirect Inc.. 

**Use** \- the treatment, handling, and management of Personal Information by the SportsDirect Inc.. 

### Principle 1 - Accountability 

SportsDirect Inc. is responsible for Personal Information under its control and shall designate one or more persons who are accountable for SportsDirect Inc.'s compliance with the following principles. 

1.1 Responsibility for ensuring compliance with the provisions of the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy rests with the senior management of SportsDirect Inc., which shall designate one or more persons to be accountable for compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy. Other people within SportsDirect Inc. may be delegated to act on behalf of the designated person(s) or to take responsibility for the day-to-day collection and processing of Personal Information. 

1.2 SportsDirect Inc. has designated a Chief Privacy Officer to oversee compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy. The Chief Privacy Officer can be contacted at Chief Privacy Officer, 77 Chain Lake Drive, Halifax, Nova Scotia, B3S 1E1. 

1.3 SportsDirect Inc. is responsible for Personal Information in its possession or control, including information that has been transferred to a Third Party for processing. SportsDirect Inc. shall use appropriate means to provide a comparable level of protection while information is being processed by a Third Party (see Principle 7). 

1.4 SportsDirect Inc. has implemented policies and procedures to give effect to the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy, including:   
a) Implementing procedures to protect Personal Information and to oversee SportsDirect Inc.'s compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy;   
b) Establishing procedures to receive and respond to inquiries or complaints;   
c) Training and communicating to staff about SportsDirect Inc.'s policies and practices; and   
d) Developing public information to explain SportsDirect Inc.'s policies and practices. 

### Principle 2 - Identifying Purposes for Collection of Personal Information 

SportsDirect Inc. has collected and collects Personal Information for the purposes set out below, and shall identify the purposes for which Personal Information is collected at or before the time the information is collected. 

2.1 SportsDirect Inc. has collected and collects Personal Information for the following purposes:   
a) To establish and maintain responsible commercial relations with Individuals and to provide ongoing service;   
b) To understand Individual needs;   
c) To develop, enhance, market or provide products and services;   
d) To meet legal or regulatory requirements, including to protect or defend a legal interest, and in connection with an actual or possible SportsDirect Inc. corporate re-organization, merger or amalgamation with another entity, or an actual or possible sale of all or a substantial portion of the assets of SportsDirect Inc., provided that the Personal Information disclosed continues to be used by the entity acquiring the information either for evaluation of the possible transaction, or, on completion of any such transaction, for the purposes permitted by this Privacy Policy. 

As examples of the above: 

i) SportsDirect Inc. may from time to time use a Person's Personal Information to contact the Person about changes, enhancements or similar notices related to SportsDirect Inc. products and services; 

ii) If a Person indicated that he/she was interested in receiving offers or information from SportsDirect Inc. or certain of our selected sponsors or advertisers, SportsDirect Inc. may send the Person materials about products and services that SportsDirect Inc. feels may be of interest to the Person; and 

iii) If a Person enters a contest or other promotion offered on a SportsDirect Inc. website, SportsDirect Inc. may, under the rules of the promotion, use the Person's name and certain other information to administer the promotion, such as contacting, announcing and promoting the winners of the promotion. 

Further references to "identified purposes" mean the purposes identified in this Principle 2. 

2.2 SportsDirect Inc. shall specify orally, electronically or in writing the identified purposes to the Person at or before the time Personal Information is collected. Upon request, persons collecting Personal Information shall explain these identified purposes or refer the Person to a designated person within SportsDirect Inc. who shall explain the purposes. 

2.3 Unless required by law, SportsDirect Inc. shall not use or disclose, for any new purpose, Personal Information that has been collected without first identifying the new purpose and obtaining the consent of the Person. 

### Principle 3 - Obtaining Consent for Collection, Use or Disclosure of Personal Information  

The knowledge and consent of a Person are required for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information, except where inappropriate. 

3.1 Generally, SportsDirect Inc. shall seek consent to use and disclose Personal Information at the same time it collects the information. However, SportsDirect Inc. may seek consent to use and disclose Personal Information after it has been collected but before it is used or disclosed for a new purpose. 

3.2 In obtaining consent, SportsDirect Inc. shall use reasonable efforts to ensure that a Person is advised of the identified purposes for which Personal Information will be used or disclosed. Purposes shall be stated in a manner that can be reasonably understood by the Person. 

3.3 SportsDirect Inc. will require Individuals to consent to the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information as a condition of the supply of a product or service only if such collection, use or disclosure is required to fulfill the identified purposes. 

3.4 In determining the appropriate form of consent, SportsDirect Inc. shall take into account the sensitivity of the Personal Information and the reasonable expectations of the Persons. 

3.5 In general, the use of products and services by an Individual constitutes implied consent for SportsDirect Inc. to collect, use and disclose Personal Information for all identified purposes. 

3.6 An Individual may withdraw consent at any time, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. Individuals may contact SportsDirect Inc. for more information regarding the implications of withdrawing consent. 

3.7 In certain circumstances Personal Information can be collected, used or disclosed without the knowledge and consent of the Person. For example, SportsDirect Inc. may collect or use Personal Information without knowledge or consent if it is clearly in the interests of the Person and consent cannot be obtained in a timely way, such as when the Person is a minor, seriously ill or mentally incapacitated. 

SportsDirect Inc. may also collect, use or disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent if seeking the consent of the Person might defeat the purpose of collecting the information such as in the investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of a federal or provincial law. 

SportsDirect Inc. may also use or disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent in the case of an emergency where the life, health or security of an individual or property is threatened. 

SportsDirect Inc. may disclose Personal Information without knowledge or consent to collect a debt, to comply with a subpoena, warrant or other court order, or as may be otherwise related to the legal or regulatory requirements described herein. 

### Principle 4 - Limiting Collection of Personal Information 

SportsDirect Inc. shall limit the collection of Personal Information to that which is necessary for the purposes identified by SportsDirect Inc.. 

SportsDirect Inc. shall collect Personal Information by fair and lawful means. 

4.1 SportsDirect Inc. collects Personal Information primarily from Individuals. 

4.2 SportsDirect Inc. may also collect Personal Information from other sources including credit bureaus, employers or personal references, or other third parties that represent that they have the right to disclose the information. 

### Principle 5 - Limiting Use, Disclosure and Retention of Personal Information 

SportsDirect Inc. shall not use or disclose Personal Information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the Person or as required by law. SportsDirect Inc. shall retain Personal Information only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected. 

5.1 In certain circumstances Personal Information can be collected, used or disclosed without the knowledge and consent of the Person. (See Principle 3.7) 

5.2 In addition, SportsDirect Inc. may disclose a Person's Personal Information to:   
a) Another person for the development, enhancement, marketing or provision of any of the products or services of SportsDirect Inc.;   
b) A person who, in the reasonable judgment of the SportsDirect Inc., is seeking the information as an agent of the Person;   
c) Any SportsDirect Inc. to permit the provision of services requested by the Person, and   
d) A Third Party or Third Parties, where the Person consents to such disclosure or disclosures is required by law. 

5.4 Only those Employees of SportsDirect Inc. who require access for business reasons, or whose duties reasonably so require, or properly designated representatives of SportsDirect Inc., are granted access to Personal Information about Individuals. 

5.5 SportsDirect Inc. shall keep Personal Information only as long as it remains necessary or relevant for the identified purposes or as required by law. Depending on the circumstances, where Personal Information has been used to make a decision about a Person, SportsDirect Inc. shall retain, for a period of time that is reasonably sufficient to allow for access by the Person, either the actual information or the rationale for making the decision. 

5.6 SportsDirect Inc. shall maintain reasonable and systematic controls, schedules and practices for information and records retention and destruction which apply to Personal Information that is no longer necessary or relevant for the identified purposes or required by law to be retained. Such information shall be destroyed, erased or made anonymous. 

### Principle 6 - Accuracy of Personal Information 

Personal Information shall be as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used. 

6.1 Personal Information used by SportsDirect Inc. shall be sufficiently accurate, complete and up-to-date to minimize the possibility that inappropriate information may be used to make a decision about a Person. 

6.2 SportsDirect Inc. shall update Personal Information about Persons as and when necessary to fulfill the identified purposes or upon notification by the Person. 

### Principle 7 - Security Safeguards 

SportsDirect Inc. shall protect Personal Information by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. 

7.1 SportsDirect Inc. shall protect Personal Information against such risks as loss or theft, unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, modification or destruction, through appropriate security measures. SportsDirect Inc. shall protect the information regardless of the format in which it is held. 

7.2 SportsDirect Inc. shall protect Personal Information disclosed to third parties by contractual agreements stipulating the confidentiality of the information and the purposes for which it is to be used. 

7.3 All employees of SportsDirect Inc. with access to Personal Information shall be required as a condition of employment to respect the confidentiality of Personal Information. 

### Principle 8 - Openness Concerning Policies and Practices 

SportsDirect Inc. shall make readily available to Persons specific information about its policies and practices relating to the management of Personal Information. 

8.1 SportsDirect Inc. shall make information about its policies and practices easy to understand, including:   
a) The title and address of the person or persons accountable for the compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy and to whom inquiries or complaints can be forwarded;   
b) The means of gaining access to Personal Information held by SportsDirect Inc.; and   
c) A description of the type of Personal Information held by SportsDirect Inc., including a general account of its use. 

8.2 SportsDirect Inc. shall make available information to help Persons exercise choices regarding the use of their Personal Information. 

### Principle 9 - Access to Personal Information 

SportsDirect Inc. shall inform a Person of the existence, use and disclosure of his or her Personal Information upon request and shall give the Person access to that information. 

A Person shall be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the Personal Information and have it amended as appropriate. 

9.1 Upon request, SportsDirect Inc. shall afford to a Person a reasonable opportunity to review the Personal Information in the Person's file. Personal Information shall be provided in understandable form within a reasonable time and at minimal or no cost to the Person. 

9.2 In certain situations, SportsDirect Inc. may not be able to provide access to all of the Personal Information that they hold about a Person. For example, SportsDirect Inc. may not provide access to information if doing so would likely reveal Personal Information about a Third Party or could reasonably be expected to threaten the life or security of another person. Also, SportsDirect Inc. may not provide access to information if disclosure would reveal confidential commercial information, if the information is protected by solicitor-client privilege, if the information was generated in the course of a formal dispute resolution process, or if the information was collected in relation to the investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of a federal or provincial law, or if the information was collected as part of journalistic, literary or artistic activities. If access to Personal Information cannot be provided, SportsDirect Inc. shall provide the reasons for denying access upon request. 

9.3 Upon request, SportsDirect Inc. shall provide an account of the use and disclosure of Personal Information and, where reasonably possible, shall state the source of the information. In providing an account of disclosure, SportsDirect Inc. shall provide a list of organizations to which it may have disclosed Personal Information about the individual when it is not possible to provide an actual list. 

9.4 In order to safeguard Personal Information, an individual or employee may be required to provide sufficient identification information to permit SportsDirect Inc. to account for the existence, use and disclosure of Personal Information and to authorize access to the individual's file. Any such information shall be used only for this purpose. 

9.5 SportsDirect Inc. shall promptly correct or complete any Personal Information found to be inaccurate or incomplete. Any unresolved differences as to accuracy or completeness shall be noted in the Person's file. Where appropriate, SportsDirect Inc. shall transmit to third parties having access to the Personal Information in question any amended information or the existence of any unresolved differences. 

9.6 A Person can obtain information or seek access to his or her Personal Information by contacting a designated representative at SportsDirect Inc. principal office. 

9.7 An employee can obtain information or seek access to his or her Personal Information by contacting his or her immediate supervisor within SportsDirect Inc.. 

### Principle 10 - Challenging Compliance 

A Person shall be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with the above principles to the designated person or persons accountable for the compliance of SportsDirect Inc. with the   
SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy. 

10.1 SportsDirect Inc. shall maintain procedures for addressing and responding to all inquiries or complaints from Persons about SportsDirect Inc.'s handling of their Personal Information. If any Person at any time has any questions or concerns about SportsDirect Inc.'s privacy practices, the Person can either: 

i) Write to: 

Customer Service - Privacy, SportsDirect Inc.   
ATT: Kelly Moss   
77 Chain Lake Drive   
Halifax, NS   
B3S 1E1 

or 

ii) Provide information to SportsDirect Inc. through our  feedback page . 

10.2 SportsDirect Inc. shall inform Persons about the existence of these procedures as well as the availability of complaint procedures. 

10.3 The person or persons accountable for compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy may seek external advice where appropriate before providing a final response to individual complaints. 

10.4 SportsDirect Inc. shall investigate all complaints concerning compliance with the SportsDirect Inc. Privacy Policy. If a complaint is found to be justified, SportsDirect Inc. shall take appropriate measures to resolve the complaint including, if necessary, amending its policies and procedures. A Person shall be informed of the outcome of the investigation regarding his or her complaint. 

Information logged by WagerLine.com

Your IP address is logged to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the site.  WagerLine.com uses cookies to save login information so you don't have to enter it each time you visit.   It also uses cookies to estimate the number of repeat visitors. 

Registration Form

WagerLine.com's registration form requires users to provide contact information (like their name and email address).  This information is used to verify eligibility of contest winners, and to contact you if you win a prize.  We may also periodically use this information to send you promotional material regarding WagerLine.com or our advertisers. 

**We never sell, give, or trade our mailing list or email list to any other company, so you can rest assured that will not receive “spam” email or be placed on any other mailing lists as a result of registering on WagerLine.com.**

Links 

WagerLine.com contains links to other sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the sites that we link.

Posting Forum 

WagerLine.com makes a posting forum available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.

Messages containing profanity, slander, libel, hatred, or obscenity are not allowed. We reserve the right to remove messages, posting rights, or user accounts at any time if this policy is not followed. Once posting rights are removed, they are not reinstated.

Free advertisements are not allowed on our posting forum for two reasons: their presence is unfair to our paying advertisers, and they often attempt to promote companies that are not reputable. Therefore, if a non-paying advertiser uses the forum to advertise their product, service, or web site; the message will be deleted and the author will permanently lose their posting rights.

Wagerline cannot and will not be held liable for the contents nor the effects of messages. The author of a post assumes all responsibility for its contents, without limits.
